============================================================================================================================================================

* Presenters…
* Browse by…

**Privacy Policy**  
We collect certain information when you visit the Lingerie Lowdown® website
================================================================================================

When you visit the Lingerie Lowdown® website, we may collect certain information or data about you and this may include:

* Questions, queries or feedback you leave, including your email address if you send an email to lingerielowdown.com
* Your IP address, and details of which version of web browser you used
* Information on how you use the site, using cookies and page tagging techniques to help us improve the website
* Details to allow you to access services and transactions, eg an email address (you’ll always be told when this information is being collected, and it will only be used for the purpose you provide it for)

This information is collected as it allows us to:

* Improve the website by monitoring how you use it
* Respond to any feedback you send us
* Provide you with information about subscriptions or other services we may provide

We can’t personally identify you using your data.

### Where your data is stored

We store your data on our secure servers in the US. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this.

### Keeping your data secure

Transmitting information over the internet is generally not completely secure, and we can’t guarantee the security of your data. Any data you transmit is at your own risk. We have procedures and security features in place to try and keep your data secure once we receive it. We won’t share your information with any other organisations for marketing, market research or commercial purposes, and we will never pass on your details to other websites.

### Disclosing your information

We may pass on your personal information if we have a legal obligation to do so, or if we have to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements.

### Your rights to have data removed

You have the right to have data we may hold on you removed. **[Contact us](https://www.lingerielowdown.com/contact/)** to ask for your details to be removed from our secure servers. Please note that if you have a valid membership, removal of data we hold will prevent you gaining access to the website.

### Links to other websites

Lingerie Lowdown® may contain links to and from other websites within it’s pages. This privacy policy only applies to this website, and doesn’t cover other websites or services that we link to.

### Following a link to another website

If you visit another website from a link found on the Lingerie Lowdown® website, read the privacy policy on that website to find out what it does with your information.

### Following a link to lingerielowdown.com from another website

If you come to lingerielowdown.com from another website, we may receive personal information about you from the other website. You should read the privacy policy of the website you came from to find out more about this.

###### Last updated: 27 January 2022

#### Lingerie Lowdown®

Your ultimate destination for unbiased lingerie and hosiery reviews and much more. Explore 12,000+ products from over 900 brands online today. Feel empowered and confident with Lingerie Lowdown, the consumer champion reviewing for over 9 years!

Your support fuels our passion to do more. With membership starting as low as £11.99 per month, you can unlock the door to the world of lingerie, hosiery and much more!

#### Follow Us

#### Get The Lowdown Newsletter

Sign up for our FREE newsletter and get access to exclusive previews and insider tips. Join our subscriber list today and be inspired!

Leave this field empty if you're human: 

© 2024 Lingerie Lowdown® Inspire • Delight • Inform
